teambuildingproject.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy    [](http://www.teambuildingproject.com/join)

The TBP intends to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. In general, you can visit the TBP on the Web without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may need information from you, such as your name and address. It is our intent to let you know before we collect personal information from you on the Internet.

If you choose to give us personal information via the Internet that we may need, it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information. If you tell us that you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes. We do keep track of the domains from which people visit us. We analyze this data for trends and statistics, and then we discard it.

We have implemented these practices for the TBP website. We intend to protect the quality and integrity of your personally identifiable information. We have implemented appropriate technical and managerial procedures to maintain information that is accurate, current, and complete. We will make a sincere effort to respond to your requests to correct personal information inaccuracies in a timely manner.

**Use of Information**

We use the information that is collected about you for a variety of purposes. You will be informed about these purposes at the time of collection. In general, however, we foresee the following uses:

**Website visitors**

Information about you may be used to add you to our email subscription list, provide your name to TBP Members in connection with your expressed interest in our products or business opportunity, analyze trends and statistics, enhance the operation of the Site, serve content and advertisements and send informational and promotional materials about TBP and other companies.

**Members**

Information about Members will in addition be used to provide training and ensure compliance with the Terms of Use.

**CHOICE**

We have existing business relationships and may develop other relationships in the future with business partners. In these instances, we may share or otherwise allow access to information that is collected about you that will enable our business partners to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest.

At the time we collect your information you will be given the choice to accept or refuse the disclosure of your information for such marketing purposes, and for marketing by TBP.

The TBP site contains links to other web sites. The TBP is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

There are various technologies, including "cookies", which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a web site. A cookie is an element of data that a web site. can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. Some of the TBP pages use cookies or other technologies so that we can better serve you when you return to our site. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it.

If you have any questions or comments about our privacy practices, please contact us via our online contact form. We will gladly answer any questions you may have.
